idvert.com 2018-10-27

# Idvert-No.1 Social Ads Spy Tool

Idvert.com (“Website”) is a website owned and operated by Idvert Co., Ltd. and/or its subsidiaries (collectively, “Idvert“, “We” or “Us“). We greatly respect your privacy, which is why we make every effort to provide a service that would live up to the highest of user privacy standards.

We understand that you care about how your information is used and shared. This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect via the Website however accessed and/or used, whether via personal computers, mobile devices or otherwise. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information you may provide to us offline. This Privacy Policy explains what information of yours will be collected by Idvert, and stored on its servers, when you make use of the Website or one of our add-ons, apps, APIs, software or downloads from the Website (“Product”), as well as how the information will be used. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time and therefore we ask you to check back periodically for the most updated version of the Privacy Policy, as indicated below. Your continued use of the Product and/or this Website after this Privacy Policy has been amended shall constitute and be deemed as your continued acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy, as amended.

If you are under 18, please do not send any personal data about yourself to us.

This policy was last updated on May 11th, 2018. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the Websites’ Terms and Conditions of Use. Each time that you access or use the Website, you agree that you have read, understand and agree to be bound by the Terms and Conditions of Use and the Privacy Policy and you expressly consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your information, including without limitation, Personally Identifiable Information, in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, “Personally Identifiable Information” or “PII” is information that we can use to identify or contact you as an individual, and includes your name, email address, address, telephone number and any other information that we associate with any of the foregoing.

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE AND THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU MUST DISCONTINUE THE WEBSITES AND ALL SERVICES AND FEATURES THEREIN.

1 Collection and Use of Information

1.1 Types of Information Collected

(a) Non-Personally Identifiable Information

Idvert collects non-personally identifying information that your browser makes available whenever you visit a website. This information includes your Internet connection and hardware specs, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your query and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

(b) Personally Identifiable Information

In addition, we collect your personal information such as your full name, credit card information, billing address, your email address, history of communication with SEMrush, history of payments, IP address, system information, and your activities on the Website.

(c) Information You Provide About A Third Party

At some Website and through certain promotions, you can submit information about other people. Please be aware that when you use any send-to-a-friend functionality on our Website, your email address may be included in the communication sent to your friend.

(d) Information We Collect from Third party websites.

Our website may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of such other Linked Sites. We encourage our users to be aware when leaving our website to read the privacy policies or statements of each Linked Site that collects your personal data. You agree to waive any claim against us with respect to the Linked Sites. We may acquire information from other trusted sources to update or supplement the information that you provided or we collected automatically.

(e) Information Collection

To facilitate your use of the Service, Idvert may automatically collect certain types of information when you access or use the Service, complete surveys, send and receive communications, perform search queries and marketing activities. In order to collect this data, Idvert may utilize automated tools and files such as cookies and web beacons. These automated tools and files may reside on our servers or on your computer or device. If you restrict our ability to use automated tools and files, your ability to access and use all or part of the Service may be limited or disabled completely.

In addition to any PII or other information that you choose to submit to us, to provide you with services and content that are more customized to your interests, We and our third-party service providers and advertisers may use a variety of technologies (including cookies, Flash cookies, web beacons and embedded scripts) (“Tracking Technologies”) that automatically or passively collect information when you visit or interact with the Website (the “Usage Information”). This Usage Information may include, without limitation, the browser that you are using, your IP address (“Identifier”), the URL that referred you to our Websites and all of the areas within our Website that you visit. We may use Usage Information for a variety of purposes.

1.2 Use and Share the Information

(a) Non-Personally Identifiable Information

Idvert uses non-personally identifying information we obtain by technical means (such as the automatic recording performed by our servers or through the use of cookies) for the above purposes and in order to monitor and analyze use of the Service, for the Service’s technical administration, to increase the Service’s functionality and user-friendliness, to better tailor it to most common user needs, to generate and derive useful data and information concerning the interests, characteristics and website use behavior of our users, and to verify that users of the Service meet the criteria required to process their requests.

(b) Personally Identifiable Information

Idvert uses the personally identifiable user information that we collect to provide, maintain, protect and improve the current Services offerings, to develop new Services, to be able to tailor the Services to one’s specific needs if feasible, for convenience of users and communication with them, and as may be required by law.

(c) Provide, Manage and Improve our Services

We may use information we collect from you in part to provide you with the goods and service you have requested, to respond to inquiries, to administer the Website and for other lawful business purposes. We also use the information in connection with advertising and to serve other content, as described below.

(d) Transactional Communications.

(e) Editorial Use.

We may use information you provide us through emails, blogs, forums, in response to polls, or through any other user generated submission for editorial purposes.

(f) Marketing. 

We may combine and use any and all information we collect on you either online or otherwise, including from third parties, for marketing purposes.

(g) Anonymous Information.

We may create anonymized information about you and other users of the Website from PII by excluding information (such as your name) that make the data personally identifiable to you.

(h)Affiliates. 

We may transfer your information, including PII, to other Idvert offices and affiliates for internal management and administrative purposes on our behalf.

(i) Social Networks. 

If you use your login credentials from a social networking site (e.g., Facebook or Twitter) on a Website if permittable, we may receive information from such social networking site in accordance with the terms and conditions (e.g., Terms and Conditions of Use and Privacy Policy) of the social networking site. If you elect to share your information with these social networking sites, we will share information with them in accordance with your election. The terms and conditions of these social networking sites will apply to the information we disclose to them.

(j) Delivery of Advertising and Other Content.

In addition to ads and content that we serve you directly, we may use third party advertising companies and marketing services to serve ads and other content when you visit the Website and elsewhere on the internet and in other media. We also use analytics services supported by third party companies to perform analytics and track trends. We work with other third parties to provide certain functionalities on the Website and to improve the effectiveness of the Website and its content. Those thir-party companies may use Tracking Technologies to collect and store Usage Information about you and may combine this information with information they collect from other sources. If you access the Website through a mobile device or app, we may also share your information with mobile carriers, operating systems and platforms.

To provide ads on the Website, we use a variety of third party advertising service providers, including networks, data exchanges, ad servers, analytics providers and others. These third parties may use technology to send, directly to your device, the advertisements and links that appear on the Website. They automatically receive your identifier when this happens. The third-party service providers, as well as the advertisers themselves, may collect and use information about your visits over time and across the Website and other third-party web sites, as well as information received from other sources, in order to serve more targeted advertising to you on the Website. Third parties may also use information gathered from your usage of the Websites to serve targeted advertisements to you on third party websites and applications. Google is one of the companies that we use to serve advertising and perform analytics on some of the Websites. We and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to help implement the above uses of your information. We also use Google Analytics along with audience data (such as age, gender and interests of users) to help understand users’ visits to the Website and to optimize the content that we serve to users.

2 Disclosure

2.1 Disclosure to Third-Parties

Idvert does not share your personal information with third parties or the public except as set forth herein. We may share your personal information with our third-party service providers, such as SMTP infrastructure providers, analytical services, payment processors, merchants, or resellers, performing services, which supplement our Services. These service providers may have access to personal information as needed to perform their functions. Third parties with whom we share your data currently include, but are not limited to, Salesforce, Google, OWOX, YouTube, Act-on, Mailchimp with Mandrill, Inspectlet, Adroll, Facebook and Twitter. We do not sell your personal information. We may offer the print and digital magazines, websites and other editorial properties published by Us (the “Publications”) through certain third party websites via subscription pages[ on such third party websites that are linked to this Privacy Policy. For the avoidance of doubt, such subscription pages are considered “Website” and this Privacy Policy applies to information collected through the subscription pages, but does not apply to information collected through the third party website.

2.2 Research and Anonymous Information

Idvert may use and disclose to third parties information we collect in aggregated, non-personally identifiable form for research and informational purposes and to help us make sales, marketing and business decisions. We may create aggregated, anonymized information about you and other users of the Websites from PII by excluding information (such as your name) that make the data personally identifiable to you (as such “Anonymous Information”). We use this Anonymous Information for any legal purpose and disclose Anonymous Information to third parties in our sole discretion.

2.3 Events and Webinars

Idvert may share the names, email addresses and other details of users who register for some of our webinars and events, both online and offline, with the respective webinar speakers, announced special guests, our partners at the events, and others. We carefully select these persons and require them to use this information for the purposes related to the event (including webinars). We will try to label such events (including webinars) on the registration forms therefor, but if you affirmatively do not wish your name, email address or other details disclosed, please contact us before registering for any event to confirm whether your personal information will be shared at the specific event that you are considering. You may not opt-out of sharing your information at an event where such information is shared. Your only recourse is not to register for an event which so shares information.

2.4 Mergers and Acquisitions

If Idvert is involved in a sale, merger, transfer, exchange, or other disposition (whether of assets, stock, or otherwise, including via bankruptcy) of all or a portion of the business conducted by the Website , we will continue to ensure the confidentiality of any personal information and give affected users notice before personal information is transferred or becomes subject to any new privacy policy of an acquirer of our business.

2.5 Special Circumstances

Idvert will not disclose your personally identifiable information except as set forth in this Section 3, including in subsections (a) through (d) below:

a. when requested to do so by law enforcement agencies;

b. for the purpose of pursuing outstanding debts or liabilities;

c. when given permission to do so by you.

3\. Your consent and rights

By using our service, making an application or visiting our website, you consent to the collection and use of your information and other activities as outlined in this policy.

You may exercise your opt-out right by notifying us if you wish to object to the use of your personal data for direct marketing purposes. Please send requests for such objections, access to data, and correction of data, information regarding policies and practices and kinds of data held, questions or complaints to our email: support@idvert.com.

4\. Security. 

We have undertaken reasonable efforts to implement administrative, technical and security safeguard to help prevent unauthorized access, use, or disclosure of the information we collect. However, no systems can be completely secure. Therefore, while we uses reasonable efforts to protect your PII, we cannot guarantee its absolute security, and your use of the Websites indicates your agreement to assume this risk.

5\. Changes to This Privacy Policy.

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice. Any changes will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Privacy Policy.

6\. Disputes; No Rights of Third Parties. 

If you choose to access the Website, use any of our services, any dispute over privacy is subject to our Terms and Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, resolution of disputes by binding arbitration, and application of the laws of the People’s Republic of China. This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties.
